shoppingsherlock.com 2014-05-10

# Privacy Policy - Shopping Sherlock - Finds you the best deals and lowest prices!

Except as described in this section, we will not sell, rent or disclose your personally identifying information to third parties without notifying you of our intent to share the information and giving you an opportunity to prevent your information from being shared. 

We occasionally use other companies, agents or contractors to perform services necessary to our operations. For example, we have partnered with companies to provide online products and services, process credit card transactions, analyze customers’ buying habits and process Associate Member and customer responses. We provide postal addresses to the U.S. Post Office, Courier Services and International Post Offices for delivery purposes. In the course of providing such services, these companies may have contact with your personal information. By contractual agreement, these companies must treat your information in accordance with this Policy. We will not be liable for any damages that may result from the misuse of your personal information by these companies. 

From time to time, we may partner with companies whose products we believe will interest our users. We may occasionally send promotional announcements to our Independent Distributors. 

Any exceptions to this policy of sharing your name, address or email address with a partner company will be done only with your permission. Best In U, Inc., Inc. also reserves the right to disclose information when required by law. We may also disclose, on an anonymous basis, literal statements made by our IA and customers. At no time will we disclose personal information about these statements without their permission. 

Customers and IAs should check back for updates to this policy. Best In U, Inc., Inc. will obtain email consent from any user if the company is going to be using the information collected in a manner different from that stated when the user registered.

SECURITY POLICY 

When transmitting your personal information to us, we use a secure server (SSL), which protects all of your personal information. This process ensures that the information you give us is protected against unauthorized access.   
You can access your account from every page on the site to update and correct your name, email address, password, postal address, and other personal profile information. Please note that you must be signed in to your online office to access this information. 

We have technology and security features, as well as strict internal guidelines, that help safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorized access or improper use. We will continue to enhance our security guidelines as new technology becomes available.
